<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - CodeStory</title><link>https://codestory.me/posts/</link><description>All Posts | CodeStory</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>sergii.lischuk@gmail.com (Sergii Lischuk)</managingEditor><webMaster>sergii.lischuk@gmail.com (Sergii Lischuk)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://codestory.me/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Content delivery network (CDN)</title><link>https://codestory.me/content-delivery-network/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2022 19:22:16 +0000</pubDate><author>Sergii Lischuk</author><guid>https://codestory.me/content-delivery-network/</guid><description>&lt;p>A content delivery network (CDN) is a geographically distributed group of servers that work together to provide fast delivery of internet content. Generally, static files such as HTML/CSS/JS, photos, and videos are served from CDN.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>7 best practices for building containers</title><link>https://codestory.me/docker-best-practice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Sergii Lischuk</author><guid>https://codestory.me/docker-best-practice/</guid><description>&lt;p>Development was always a way of evolution. The evolution of modern programming development brings a lot of techniques and requirements - its hard to imagine today&amp;rsquo;s programming without high-level frameworks, containers, cloud computing or special data storages (even if they are not necessary). Working with some of them, I would like to share small notes about the containerization, especially with Docker containers.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Caching responses in http client</title><link>https://codestory.me/httpclient-cache-response/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Sergii Lischuk</author><guid>https://codestory.me/httpclient-cache-response/</guid><description>&lt;p>Working with high-load systems or with a system where it is important to have a good response time - the cache is a first citizen. This package contains lightweight, self-written, in-memory cache implementation to catch and store responses based on their status code. The configuration is pretty flexible and gives opportunity to set pair between cache time and response code.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>